Your BFF, Ryugamine Mikado, is the leader of the Dollars.
ダラーズのボスは 君の大事な大親友 竜ヶ峰帝人君さ
その集会に案内してください
Please take me to that meeting.
We'll take you up on your offer to fight.
売られたケンカは受けて立つぜ
If there's a faction that's friends with the black biker and is targeting the Yellow Scarves...
ダラーズに黒バイクを仲間とする派閥があって
そいつらが 黄巾賊を狙い撃ちしているとしたら…
It'll simply turn into a real conflict if things keep going like this.
このまま進めば 本当の抗争になるだけさ
I'll remove that crap from reality!
現実からは駆逐してやる オレら黄巾賊がな！
We're the Yellow Scarves!
I didn't quit back then.
あのとき 僕はやめなかった
At the time, why didn't I...?
あのとき 僕は どうして…
Did Masaomi...say anything?
正臣 なんか言ってた？
Kida?
紀田？
No, I haven't seen him yet.
いや ここには来てないけど
It's not like I suspect him or anything.
別に竜ヶ峰のことを疑ったりしてないから
You guys said you didn't tell anyone that I'm in the Dollars, right?
オレがダラーズだって 誰にも言ってないんだろ？
Oh...yeah.
うん…
This isn't something you should feel responsible for.
お前らが責任を感じることじゃないよ
I've...decided to quit the Dollars.
オレ ダラーズ やめることにした
It's stopped being colorless.
もう 透明じゃなくなっちまったからな
I see...
そう…
I've been thinking about it for a while, but maybe you're in the—
前から気になってたんだけど
お前も ひょっとして ダラーズ…
違う！
No!
Alright.
そっか…
That day, he said:
あの日 あの人は言っていた
"But once you step into that world, it'll only take about three days for that to seem normal, too."
でも そっち側も踏み込めば
たぶん３日で 日常になってしまうんだろうね
"If you truly want to escape from everyday life, you've no other choice but to keep evolving."
本当に日常から脱却したければ
常に進化し続けるしかないんだよ
"No matter whether you're aiming higher or lower."
I decided to keep evolving.
進化してやろうって 決めた
But...
でも…
Is this...the result?
これが その結果…
Your call will be forwarded to an answering machine.
留守番電話サービスにつなぎます
So, weren't you listening?
で 聞いてなかった？
I said, "No more fighting."
オレ 小競り合いは禁止だって 言ったよな？
But...
でも…
...Didn't I?
言ったよなぁ
Sh-Shogun! Is it alright to keep going on like this?
しょ… 将軍 このままでいいんですか？
It's a fact that the headless rider is part of the Dollars!
首なしライダーがダラーズなのは 間違いねぇんだよ！
You just want us to grin and bear it while they make us look like idiots?!
このままなめたマネされて 黙ってるんですか～!
Plus, the Dollars' leader might show himself if we keep this up.
それに こうやってりゃ ダラーズのリーダーとやらが姿を現すかもしれないっすよ
I'll investigate the identity of the Dollars' leader a bit longer.
ダラーズのリーダーについては もう少し探りを入れてみる
Don't do anything until I find out something more concrete.
確かなことが分かるまで おとなしくしてろ
Got it?!
分かったな！
Either way, you can't stop us.
どっちみち もう止められやしねぇよ
It's nothing to worry about.
Even if that hadn't happened,
何もなかったとしても いつかこういう事態に なったのかもしれないし
it probably would have turned out like this anyway.
I wonder...
そうなんでしょうか？
There are lots of fights like that in this city...
この街じゃ ああいうケンカはよくあることっていうか
And it's nobody's fault that someone who
goes to the same school as you got attacked.
同じ学校の子が襲われたのも 誰のせいでもない
So don't worry about it.
だから 気にしないで
The Dollars...
Are you one of them?
Got it?
Alright, I'm leaving this private conversation.
じゃ 内緒モードからでるよ？
Okay?
Huh?!
Hey, you!
おい こら！ ぶつかっといて あいさつもなしか!
You're not going to say anything even after you bumped into me?!
Wait...
Heiwajima...
へ… 平和島…
Shizu—
Yeah.
Huh?!
It's such a nice night.
Hey, Shizuo!
おい 静雄～！
Yo.
Sorry about that.
He's also in the Dollars, right?
あいつもダラーズだったよな？
ああ 半年前の集会にいたって
Yeah, he was at that gathering six months ago.
Idiot! Heiwajima Shizuo and that black guy from Russia Sushi are exceptions!
バカ！ 平和島静雄と「露西亜寿し」の黒人は例外なんだよ！
Don't lay a hand on them unless you want to die.
死にたくなきゃ 手ぇ出すんじゃねぇぞ
Yo.
Uh, hello.
どうも
You're alone?
一人か？ 紀田は一緒じゃないのか？
Kida isn't with you?
はあ… 正臣に何か？
Did you want to talk to Masaomi?
Not really. It's just dangerous roaming around by yourself.
別に 一人でぶらついてると 危ないぞ
A Raira student got attacked, you know.
来良の生徒もやられたんだろ？
Did you know him?
知り合いか？
I see...
そうか…
Th-Thank you very much.
あっ ありがとうございます
This town's been in an uproar ever since that thing with the Slasher.
斬り裂き魔の一件以来 騒がしいな
I heard that the Yellow Scarves are gunning for the Dollars...
黄巾賊の人たちはダラーズを目の敵にしてるって聞いてますけど…
The Dollars haven't attacked anyone.
ダラーズからは手出ししていない
The boss hasn't issued any real orders, either.
ボスからも特に指示は出ていない
It seems that some people are worried about that...
そのことに不満を抱いている連中もいるようだが…
Well, it's just a rumor anyway.
まあ あくまで噂だがな
Are you in the Dollars, Kadota?
門田さんはダラーズなんですか？
No. Why?
いや… どうしてだ？
I've been wondering if it's really okay for the Dollars to exist.
ダラーズなんて 本当にあっていいのかなって思って…
Is the Dollars really necessary?
ダラーズなんて 本当に必要なんでしょうか？
Who knows...
さあな…
Even Mikado...
帝人までこんなときに…
I see.
なるほど 君は罪歌
So, you were having a private conversation with Saika—Sonohara Anri.
園原杏里ちゃんと内緒モードでやり取りをしていた
Except she wouldn't respond to you no matter how much you typed.
しかし どれだけ書き込んでも レスがない
Well, I figured she'd be depressed, seeing as how things are.
まあ 事態が事態だし よっぽど落ち込んでいるんだろうと思っていた
However...
ところが…
What about her cell phone?
杏里ちゃんの携帯は？ 通じないの？
Can you reach her?
It seems like she turned it off.
電源を切ってるみたいだ
Anyway, what's up with Kanra?
それにしても 何なんだ？ 甘楽ってヤツは
He's just writing stuff that'll make Anri worried...
杏里ちゃんを不安にさせるようなことばかり書いて
By Anri, you mean the Sonoharas' daughter?
杏里ちゃんって 園原堂のお嬢さんだったよね？
Yeah...
うん
The daughter of that antique salesman who sold Saika...
おやじが罪歌を売った古物商の娘さんか…
The leader of the Dollars is her classmate,
で ダラーズのリーダーはその子の同級生で
and she has a friend in the Yellow Scarves as well.
黄巾賊にも友達がいる
Anri doesn't know that Mikado is the leader of the Dollars.
帝人がダラーズのリーダーだってことは 杏里ちゃんは知らないんだ
Anyway, the three of them are friends, and neither the Dollars kid nor the Yellow Scarves kid know about her.
とにかく 三人は仲よしで
ダラーズの子と黄巾賊の子は お互いにそのことを知らない
Probably...
たぶん…
I haven't asked her much about it.
私も詳しいことは聞いてないんだ
Sorry, but please don't ask.
すみません 何も聞かないでください
I'm sorry.
すみません
A regular gathering of the triumvirate.
まさに三頭両緒って感じだね
So, what're you going to do?
で 君はどうするんだい？
I can't say anything if Anri's going to stay quiet, can I?
杏里ちゃんが黙っているのに 私が口を出すわけにはいかないだろう？
All I can do is pray for their safety.
三人の無事を祈るしかない
Heyoooo!
It's Kanra!
Oh my, there's not a soul around.
You didn't leave me behind to go do something fun, did you?
Hmph!
But, that's okay.
I'm basking in my praise!
The game's getting really interesting, so I'll log off, too!
Bye byes!
Kanra has left the chat room.
There is currently no one in the chat room.
A number of days passed.
何日かたった
I haven't been to the Dollars' website since.
あれ以来 僕はダラーズのサイトを見ていない
The uproar that's gripped the city is apparently still going on.
街では相変わらず騒ぎが続いているらしい
However, my everyday life here hasn't changed.
でも ここでの僕の日常に変わりはない
Also, Takeguchi was released from the hospital.
滝口君も退院した
If I stay like this, I can live in peace.
こうしていれば 平和でいられる
This is my everyday life.
これが 僕の日常…
But...
でも…
Huh? Kida's already gone home.
えっ？ 紀田なら もう帰ったぜ
Thanks for visiting me.
見舞い ありがとな
Um...
あの… 私 今日はここで…
This is it for me today.
I see...
そう…
Then...
じゃあ
See you tomorrow.
また明日
Hey, you're in the Dollars, aren't you?
こら！ おめぇ ダラーズだろう？
N-No I'm not!
ち… 違います！
Of course you are.
決まってんだよ ダラーズって…
Eh?
Huh?
Please run while you can.
今のうちに逃げてください
What're you doing?!
何すんだ おめぇ…
A-Are you going to betray us?!
て… てめぇら 裏切るのか!
Mother has asked us...
「母さん」に頼まれましたから
Mother has asked us to put a stop to you.
あなたたちを止めろと 「母さん」に頼まれたんです
If it looks like anyone from the Yellow Scarves is
about to attack someone in the Dollars, please stop them.
黄巾賊の人がダラーズの人を襲いそうになったら
止めてください
Yes. I understand, Mother.
はい 分かりました 「母さん」
Please, I'm counting on you.
すみません お願いします
Huh?
It's my fault.
私のせいだ…
It's my fault that Kida...
私のせいで 紀田君が…
Is there anyone in the Yellow Scarves who can hear my voice?
誰か 黄巾賊の方の中で私の声が聞こえる方 いませんか？
I have to do something.
なんとかしなきゃ
I have to...
なんとか… なんとかしなきゃ！
I have to do something.
Hello?
もっしも～し クイーンをＣのケの６へ  黒をＧのカの６へ
Queen to C-Ke-6.
Black to G-Ka-6.
Good, good.
いいね いいね～ 盛り上がってきた
This is getting interesting.
Hey! Spit it out! C'mon!
こらぁ！ 言ってみろや こらっ！
I-I really don't have any idea...
なんのことだか ほんとに
What? I can't hear you...
聞こえねぇなぁ
You don't remember, huh? Don't screw with us!
覚えてねぇだと？ ふざけんな こら！
It's the truth!
That's enough.
そのへんにしとけって
But we need to make an example of them for—
それじゃ 下の者に示しが…
Do you really not remember anything?
おめぇら 本当になんも覚えてねぇのか？
When we came to, everyone was angry at us...
気がついたら みんなが怒ってて…
It's true! It's true!
ほんとっす ほんとっす～
Could it be hypnosis?
まさか催眠術？
Like, "You're getting very sleepy?"
あなたは だんだん眠くなる～ってか？
It may actually have been hypnosis.
本当に催眠術かもしれませんよ
Huh?
I mean...Right?
だって… なあ
Yeah...
If the Dollars have the headless rider,
hypnosis should be easy for them.
ダラーズには首なしライダーがいるから
催眠術くらい…
Umm...
あの…
What is it?
なんだ？
Sir, I saw them with a girl.
はい こいつらが女と一緒にいるのを見ました
A girl?
女？
Now that you mention it...
そういえば…
I did, too.
オレも見ました
I feel like they started acting weird after meeting with that girl.
その女と会ってから こいつら様子がおかしくなっちまった気がするんです
What's she look like?
どんな女だ？
Sir, she wore a Raira uniform...
はい 来良の制服を着て
had glasses...
眼鏡を掛けていて
a-and big breasts...
むっ… 胸が大きかったような…
The girl on the headless rider's bike also wore glasses, didn't she?
首なしライダーと乗り込んできた女も眼鏡だったよな？
No...
いや
She had big tits, too.
It couldn't be...
ありえねぇ…
You got a pretty good look despite the situation, huh?
It couldn't be...
ありえねぇよ
Alright, let's capture this girl and—
おっしゃ～！ その女 捕まえて…
No!
よせ！
I told you already...
言ったはずだ 小競り合いは禁止だってな
No more fighting!
If we bring her into this, then—
その女 引っ張ってくりゃ…
You all understand, don't you?
お前たちも分かったな
Don't start anything until I say it's okay.
オレがいいって言うまで 勝手に手ぇ出すんじゃねぇぞ
Yes, sir!
はい！
It's not true.
うそだろ？ うそだよな？
It's not true, is it?
I mean...
だって… だってよ
She...
あいつは… 杏里は…
Anri...
If you show them to Mika...
Really? Then I'll show her my notes.
マジで？
じゃ… じゃあ 逆にオレもノート見せる
I don't even remember her!
あんたのノートは いつも使えないの
You're useless.
Huh?
あれ？ なんだろう？
What is it?
Something's weird.
なんか変だ
That's right, neither Masaomi nor Sonohara are here.
そっか…
正臣も園原さんもいないんだ
So this is how vast this city feels when you're alone.
一人でいると こんなに広い街だったんだ
I remember thinking I wanted to go home when I first got here.
初めて来たときは 帰りたいって思ったっけ
But I met lots of people and experienced many
things while Masaomi was showing me around,
でも 正臣に案内されているうちに
いろんな人と出会って
いろんなことを経験して
so I feel like this city has become my own now.
今ではすっかり自分の街になったような気がしていた
Yet...
けど あの中にもきっと ダラーズのメンバーがいる…
There have to be members of the Dollars amongst them...
Ryugamine?
竜ヶ峰君？
What timing!
ちょうどよかった
I have something to ask you.
ねえ 話があるんだけど
U-Um, Harima...
あの～ 張間さん
What did you need to ask me?
僕に話って…
Oh, that's right.
そうそう 最近 杏里ちゃんだけどさ
What's gotten into Anri recently?
一体どうしたの？
What do you mean, "What's gotten into her?"
どうしたって… 何が？
Ryugamine, you haven't noticed at all?
ひょっとして 竜ヶ峰君 気づいてないの？
Huh? Noticed what?
えっ？ 何に？
It seems like something's been bothering Anri recently.
杏里ちゃん ここしばらく悩んでたみたいだよ
That obviously made me worry, so I asked her
what was wrong, but she just kept saying, "I'm fine."
私もさすがに気になったから 聞いてみたんだけど
そしたら なんかもう「大丈夫ですから」の一点張りなんだもん
Anri's always been the type to bottle stuff up, so I'm worried.
I hadn't noticed at all.
全然何も気づいてなかった…
So I figured that she might have told you something.
で 竜ヶ峰君なら何か聞いてるんじゃないかな～ って 思ったんだけどな
No, I haven't heard anything...
いや 僕は何も…
Hmm. I see.
そっか
I'll ask her later.
今度 聞いてみるよ
If you find out anything, tell me.
そう 何か分かったら 教えてよね
Okay.
うん
That's all.
それだけ
Let's go, Seiji!
じゃあ 行きましょ 誠二さん
Ryugamine.
竜ヶ峰
You love Sonohara, don't you?
お前さ 園原のこと 好きなんだろ？
Well, er, um...Why?
あっ いや その… な… なんで？
Don't play dumb. Anyone can tell by looking at you.
ごまかすなよ 見てれば分かるさ
If you truly love her, don't turn a blind eye to her.
本当に好きなら 何があっても目をそらすな
No matter what you learn about your partner or see her do, don't turn a blind eye to it.
相手の何を知っても 何を見ても
目を背けるな
Don't let go of the arms that embrace you.
抱き締めた腕を 絶対に離しちゃダメだ
That's your responsibility as a lover.
それが 愛すると決めた者の責任だ
See you.
じゃあな
Wow! I'll also fulfill my responsibility to love you!
私も誠二さんのこと責任を持って 愛しま～す！
Yagiri's a weird guy...
矢霧君はおかしな人だけど
...but I thought he seemed kind of cool.
でも
少しだけ かっこいいと思った
ったく… くそっ！
Damn! Unbelievable...
That little brat acting all tough...
ガキがでけぇ面しやがって くそ～…
Yeah, there's something weird going on.
将軍 なんかおかしいっすよね
Oh, Horada!
法螺田さん！ あれ
Huh?
Over there!
Hm?
Oh?
A Raira uniform...
来良の制服…
Glasses...
眼鏡！
No matter what you learn or see...
何を知っても 何を見ても 目を背けない
...don't turn a blind eye.
Take...
責任…
I had no idea...that Sonohara was worried about anything.
園原さんが何かに悩んでいるなんて 気がつかなかった
What about Masaomi?
正臣は？ 正臣は気づいていたのかな？
Did he notice?
I might not have noticed anything
because I've only been thinking about myself.
自分のことばっかりで 何も見てなかったのかもしれない
Concerning Sonohara as well as the Dollars...
園原さんのことも ダラーズのことも
What...do I know about the Dollars?
僕は ダラーズの何を知ってるんだろう？
Why didn't I...quit the Dollars back then?
どうしてあのとき ダラーズをやめてしまわなかったんだろう？
I'm leaving the Dollars.
Don't keep writing that!
I'll kill the Yellow Scarves.
That's why our leader needs to do something!
Who's our leader, anyway?!
Do you think the Dollars should exist?
We don't need it anymore.
You're just saying you're quitting, aren't you?
I said, "Don't keep writing that!"
I don't want it to go away. That's why I
want our leader to do something about it.
Our leader should take some responsibility,
since he started the Dollars.
What responsibility? No one's above or below anyone else;
We're all free. Isn't that what the Dollars is all about?
Don't rely only on a boss in times like this.
Come to think of it, I remember
someone posted something like this before:
He said we should turn the Dollars
into a good group by our own power.
There may be bad people in this
group, but don't worry about them.
Maybe this doesn't have anything to do with a leader.
That's right! The Dollars isn't someone's group, it's all of ours!
Yuck.
We should just do what we can by ourselves.
Go die.
I agree! We should protect this city
from the Yellow Scarves by ourselves!
You mean like go on patrol?
They don't know who we are, since we're "clearly colorless," so we can all help each other!
That's right.
そうだ…
That's right!
そうだった
Like before...
あのときも…
A Raira uniform...
来良で 眼鏡で
Glasses...
Breasts...
胸…
It couldn't be!
まさか…
Sonohara...!
園原さん？
Black has surrounded white's queen...
クイーンが黒に囲まれた
No way!
うそ…
It couldn't be!
まさか そんなこと…
That can't...
制作：lastzzz akira 安静の云
Is this a dream?
これは夢？
No.
違う 彼の手がそう教えてくれていた
That's what he told me.
漫游字幕组
http://popgo.net/bbs
How come you never notice what's important until it's too late?
大事なことは なぜ気づいたときには失っているんだろう？
Next Time: Break-Up Announcement.